{
  "id": "MA3144",
  "IntroText": {
    "Type": "PlainText",
    "Content": "填填看，完成公斤和公克的換算"
  },
  "GameType": "SelfDefine",
  "GameConfig": {},
  "Hint": {},
  "Questions": [
    [
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "5公斤",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "g": 5000
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 4,
              "answer": 5000
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "3公斤",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "g": 3000
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 4,
              "answer": 3000
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "6公斤",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "g": 6000
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 4,
              "answer": 6000
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "2公斤",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "g": 2000
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 4,
              "answer": 2000
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "1公斤",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "g": 1000
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 4,
              "answer": 1000
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "1公斤300公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "g": 1300
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 4,
              "answer": 1300
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "2公斤400公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "g": 2400
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 4,
              "answer": 2400
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "3公斤500公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "g": 3500
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 4,
              "answer": 3500
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "4公斤200公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "g": 4200
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 4,
              "answer": 4200
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "5公斤100公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "g": 5100
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 4,
              "answer": 5100
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "8000公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "kg": 8
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "kg",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 2,
              "answer": 8
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "9000公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "kg": 9
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "kg",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 2,
              "answer": 9
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "7000公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "kg": 7
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "kg",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 2,
              "answer": 7
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "6000公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "kg": 6
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "kg",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 2,
              "answer": 6
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "5000公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "kg": 5
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "kg",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 2,
              "answer": 5
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "9040公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "kg": 9,
          "g": 40
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "kg",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 2,
              "answer": 9
            }
          },
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 3,
              "answer": 40
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "8050公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "kg": 8,
          "g": 50
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "kg",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 2,
              "answer": 8
            }
          },
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 3,
              "answer": 50
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "1040公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "kg": 1,
          "g": 40
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "kg",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 2,
              "answer": 1
            }
          },
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 3,
              "answer": 40
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "2020公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "kg": 2,
          "g": 20
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "kg",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 2,
              "answer": 2
            }
          },
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 3,
              "answer": 20
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "5010公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "kg": 5,
          "g": 10
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "kg",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 2,
              "answer": 1
            }
          },
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 3,
              "answer": 9
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "1009公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "kg": 1,
          "g": 9
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "kg",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 2
            }
          },
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 3
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "2005公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "kg": 2,
          "g": 5
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "kg",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 2,
              "answer": 2
            }
          },
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 3,
              "answer": 5
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "3006公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "kg": 3,
          "g": 6
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "kg",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 2,
              "answer": 3
            }
          },
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 3,
              "answer": 6
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "5001公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "kg": 5,
          "g": 1
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "kg",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 2,
              "answer": 5
            }
          },
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 3,
              "answer": 1
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "QuestionDescription": {
          "Text": "公斤與公克的換算",
          "Size": "title-medium"
        },
        "HintText": "提示：1公斤=1000公克",
        "Question": "8007公克",
        "correctAnswer": {
          "kg": 8,
          "g": 7
        },
        "answerFormat": [
          {
            "unit": "kg",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 2,
              "answer": 8
            }
          },
          {
            "unit": "g",
            "Data": {
              "digitCount": 3,
              "answer": 7
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  ]
}
